

LE TIEN

Environmental Engineer

Contact



0866961606



June 16, 1998



tienle166@gmail.com



Ha Noi, Viet Nam

About Me

Dedicated and detail-oriented HSE Officer with 2.5 years of experience in promoting workplace safety and regulatory compliance. Aiming to advance safety culture and operational performance through proactive risk management and continuous improvement initiatives.

H Skills

- Language skill: TOEIC 890 (2023) & 6.5 IELTS (2016)
- Computer skill: PowerBI, Word, Excel, Powerpoint
- Personal skill: Professional communication skill & Time management skill with ability to prioritize the tasks while meeting deadlines.

Education

Rejto Sandor Faculty of Light Industry and Environmental Protection Engineering

OBUDA University

2017 - 2022

Bachelor of Science in Environmental Engineering and has qualified as an Environmental Engineer



Experience

SHE Engineer

UNILEVER VIETNAM

December 2023 - Now

- Assist SHE Manager to review the current system in whole country such as SHE frame work standards & specific standards and other external certificate ISO45001. Ensure the compliant and take action required.
- Create and maintain SHE Power BI Dashboard to do statistical analysis, data analysis for reporting to management team on all issues.
- Translate of SHE materials training then circulate & follow up actions.
- Lead Warehouse Audit at Linfox (VSIP Bac Ninh).
- Lead the Safety Assessment for offsite event and Go-to-market team in the North.

HSE Engineer

May 2022 - November 2023

OBAYASHI VIETNAM CORPORATION

- Assist Management Representative in establishing, implementing, maintaining, improving activities of OH&S System.
- Monitor sites at HaiPhong (Dinh Vu, Nomura Industrial Zone) and Hanoi (Aeonmall LongBien), Hue (Aeonmall Hue),... safety performance, implementation of safety objectives in order to control the trend of safety risk.
- Coordinate with BSI company in ISO 45001 re-certification audit for Obayashi Vietnam Corporation.
- Implement ISO 14001:2015 Environmental Management System for Obayashi Vietnam Corporation.

Intern

June 2020 - August 2020

HUNGARY AGRO-ENVIRONMENTAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE

- Write scientific reports and datasheets related to algae and water fleas.
- Examine the decomposition of herbicides.

Certifications

- CQI and IRCA Certified ISO 45001:2018 Lead Auditor (Qualified)
- ISO 14001:2015 Environment Management Systems (EMS) Awareness and Internal Auditor (Attendee)
- ISO 9001:2015 Quality Management Systems (QMS) Awareness and Internal Auditor (Attendee)
- ISO 45001:2015 Occupational Health Management System (OH&S)
 Awereness and Internal Auditor (Attendee)